Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 74, folder: 1 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: How Westinghouse Personalizes Benefits to Each Employee, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Management Counseling, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Box: 74, folder: 2 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Management Salary Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. June 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Westinghous's Work Simplification Saves $2,500 Per Supervisor, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    By Wells Norris. Sept. and Oct, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Office Management Work Simplification, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Management Position Description and Analysis Form, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Personal Record of Benefits Unde the Westinghouse Pension and Insurance Plans, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Your Westinghouse Benefits Are There When You Need Them, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Your Westinghouse Benefits Are There When You Need Them, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The New Westinghouse Pay Raise Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. November, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Management Guide and Salary Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Management Position Description and Analysis Form, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: The Merit Plan for Management Salary Increases, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Box: 74, folder: 3 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: This Way Up, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. The Westinghouse Manufacturing Training Program for College Grads. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Westinghouse Graduate Student Training Program, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Westinghouse Graduate Study Program Announcement of Courses, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Management Seminar for Section Chiefs, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    By Western Electric Co., Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Continued Education for Westinghouse Profession Panel, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    By Westinghouse Training and Development Dept. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Appentice School, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: It's Your Decision, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: It's Your Decision- Leader's Guide, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: How Westinghouse Approaches Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Continued Education for Westinghouse Professional Personnel, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Conducting Small Group Meetings- Leader's Guide, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Box: 74, folder: 4 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The University College of the West Indies, Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    By T.W.J. Taylor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report on Experimental Training Programme for Foremen, Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    By University College of the West Indies. June-September, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Programme for Third Series of Three Linked Week-End Schools on The Role of the Foreman in Industry, Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    By University College of the West Indies. September-October, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Some Notes on the Educaional Programme in Industrial Relations Extra-Mural Department, Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    By University College of the West Indies. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Some Notes on the Educational Programme in Industrial Relations Extra-Mural Department, Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    By University College of the West Indies. copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 5 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report on the Industrial Relations Programme of the Department of Extramural Studies, Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
    By University College of the West Indies. April 1959-August 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Citizens Committee to Suppot GE Strikers, Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
    By Youth Committee to Support the GE Workers. February 7, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Why Engineering Students Should Support the Strike Against General Electric, Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
    By Youth Committee to Support the GE Workers. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 6 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A Brief Summary of the Extras in Your Job, Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
    By West Penn Power Company. September 1960. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 7 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report to Shareholders, Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
    By Westvaco Corp. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 8 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Regulations of the Commissioner, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
    By West Virginia Department of Employment Security. revised January 1, 1963; effective August 15, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 9 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Bylaws, Publication (Box 74, Folder 9)
    By West Virginia Nurses Association. amended October 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 10 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: House Bill No. 115, Publication (Box 74, Folder 10)
    By West Virginia Human Rights Commission. passed on March 6, 1961; effective on July 1, 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 11 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: New York Society of Security Analysts, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
    By West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company. December 7, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Westvaco- The New Name of West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: A Story of Papermaking, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Papermaking, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Pulp and Papermaking, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
    By W. C. Andrews. July 29, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Pulp and Paper Mill Diagram, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Panorama of Papermaking Today, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Box: 74, folder: 12 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Annual Meeting Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 12)
    By West Virginia Pulp and Paper. March 22, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 74, Folder 12)
    By West Virginia Pulp and Paper. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 13 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Welcome, Publication (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Graduate Program in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 74, Folder 13)
    By West Virginia University. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Statement on Structure and Activities of The Institute of Management and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 74, Folder 13)
    By Rutgers University. May 25, 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 14 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A Reprint of a Talk by President Norton Clapp, Publication (Box 74, Folder 14)
    By Weyerhauser Company. at Company Executive Conference; March 2, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Room at the Top, Publication (Box 74, Folder 14)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Weyerhaeuser News, Publication (Box 74, Folder 14)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. July 1960. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 15 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Room at the Top, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Handy Facts About Weyerhaeuser, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: From Weyerhaeuser Tree Farms to You, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Progress in Air and Water Protection, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: A History of Weyerhaeuser Company, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. 9/13/66. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Dynamic Force in Paper, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: From Weyerhaeuser Tree Farms to You, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Weyerhaeuser Timber: Out of the Woods, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
    By Seymour Freedgood. July 1959; Fortune. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Forest Products from Tree Farm to You, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Of Trees and Men: The Story of the Weyerhaeuser Companies, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: The Weyerhaeuser High Yield Forest, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Weyerhaeuse: What It Is, Where It's Going, And How It Is Working on Tomorrow's Ideas Today., Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Box: 74, folder: 16 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: "The River That Doesn't Flow Becomes Stagnant", Publication (Box 74, Folder 16)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. a reprint of President Norton Clapp's talk at the Company Executive Conference; March 2, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Room At The Top, Publication (Box 74, Folder 16)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. Weyerhaeuser Today. A growth company where young men are on the move. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Weyerhaeuser News, Publication (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Box: 74, folder: 17 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Treasure of the Timberlands, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Jim Breetveld. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Weyerhaeuser Magazine, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. April 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Interim Report to Shareholders for the Period Ending June 29, 1969, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. July 21, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: 1968 Annual Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Weyerhaeuser World, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. vol. 1, no. 3; September 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Tacoma Newsletter, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. vol. 4, no. 9; October 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Weyerhaeuser Magazine, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. May 1964; vol. 16, no. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Weyerhaeuser Magazine, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. September 1964; vol. 16, no. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Weyerhaeuser Magazine, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. vol. 16, no. 6; October 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Weyerhaeuser Magazine, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. vol. 16, no.3; March 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Plain Talk About Trees and Taxes, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    By Weyerhaeuser Company. infogram sheet also included. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Weyerhaeuser 1965 Annual Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Box: 74, folder: 18 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Index to State Reports, Publication (Box 74, Folder 18)
    By White House Conference. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 19 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Primer for Counselor in Industry, Publication (Box 74, Folder 19)
    By Gladys D. Meyer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employer Attitudes: Implications of an Aging Work Force, Publication (Box 74, Folder 19)
    By William M. Mercer, Inc. information kit; November 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Roper Public Opinion Research Center, Publication (Box 74, Folder 19)
    By Williams College. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 20 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Our Company, Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    By Williamson-Dickie Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 21 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 74, Folder 21)
    By Williamson Heater Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 22 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Plan of Group Life Insurance for Employes of Wilson & Co., Inc., Publication (Box 74, Folder 22)
    By Wilson & Co., Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Mutual benefit Fund Providing Disability, Medical, and Death Benefits for Wilson & Co. Employes, Publication (Box 74, Folder 22)
    By Wilson & Co., Inc. memo on changes made since booklet printing dated 9/8/1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Hospital Surgical Medical Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 74, Folder 22)
    By Wilson & Co., Inc. established on Dec. 1 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Long Term Salary Continuance Insurance for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Welcome to Wilson, Publication (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: The Wilson Employees' Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 22)
    By Wilson & Co., Inc. information booklet; 6th edition; January 1, 1965, effective 1/1/1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 23 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Wilson, Publication (Box 74, Folder 23)
    By Wilson & Co. brochure. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Welcome to Wilson, Publication (Box 74, Folder 23)
    By Wilson & Co. brochure; copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Welcome to Wilson, Publication (Box 74, Folder 23)
    By Wilson & Co. brochure; copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Welcome to Wilson, Publication (Box 74, Folder 23)
    By Wilson & Co. brochure; copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Welcome to Wilson, Publication (Box 74, Folder 23)
    By Wilson & Co. Wilson's certified brochure (different version). Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 24 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Wilson Certified News, Publication (Box 74, Folder 24)
    By Wilson & Co. February 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wilson's Certified News, Publication (Box 74, Folder 24)
    By Wilson & Co. December 1951; includes "The Christmas Story" illistrated by Stryker Ingerman. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 74, Folder 24)
    By Wilson & Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 25 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Annual Report of the Woodrow Wilson Foundation: 1948-1949, Publication (Box 74, Folder 25)
- Box: 74, folder: 26 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Careers: Wisconsin State Government, Publication (Box 74, Folder 26)
    By Wisconsin Bureau of Personnel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Opportunities for College Seniors and Graduates, Publication (Box 74, Folder 26)
    By Wisconsin Bureau of Personnel. for 1966-1967 program. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Wage, Salary, and Fringe Benefit Survey Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 26)
    By Wisconsin Bureau of Personnel. February 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 27 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: A Review of the "Current Employment Statistics" Program in Wisconsin, Publication (Box 74, Folder 27)
    By Wisconsin Department of Industry, Labor, and Human Relations. preented at a meeting of WSES Local Office Managers and Labor Market Analysts on June 29, 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 28 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Wisconsin Electric Power Company's Story, Publication (Box 74, Folder 28)
    By Wisconsin Electric Power Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 29 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Job Application and Rating Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: You and the Electric Company, Publication (Box 74, Folder 29)
    By Wisconsin Electric Power Company. October 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 30 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Diary of a Dollar, Publication (Box 74, Folder 30)
    By Wisconsin Electric Power Company. Employes' News (news magazine of Wisconsin Power & Light Company) vol. 26, no. 2; February 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Foremen's Conference Newsletter, Publication (Box 74, Folder 30)
    By Wisconsin Electric Power Company. May 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Customer Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 74, Folder 30)
    By Wisconsin Electric Power Company. bulletin no. 96, meeting no. 94; June 11, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Foremen's Conference Newsletter, Publication (Box 74, Folder 30)
    By Wisconsin Electric Power Company. June 1951. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 31 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Wisconsin Administrative Code, Publication (Box 74, Folder 31)
    By Wisconsin Employment Relations Board. from the Wisconsin Employment Relations Board; effective May 1, 1958. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 32 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: State of Wisconsin, Publication (Box 74, Folder 32)
    By Wisconsin Governor's Commission on Human Rights. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 33 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: 1965 Annual Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 33)
    By Wisconsin Power & Light Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 34 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The State Historical Society of Wisconsin, Madison, Publication (Box 74, Folder 34)
    By Wisconsin State Historical Society. The Society Press. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 35 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research Institute News, Publication (Box 74, Folder 35)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: IRRI Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 35)
    By The University of Wisconsin. February 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The School for Workers, Publication (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: The School for Workers, Publication (Box 74, Folder 35)
- Box: 74, folder: 36 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Motivation for Increased Productivity, Publication (Box 74, Folder 36)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Wisconsin University Center for Motivation. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 37 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Motivation for Increased Productivity, Publication (Box 74, Folder 37)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Wisconsin University School for Workers; The Center for Motivation, School of Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Center for Productivity Motivation, Publication (Box 74, Folder 37)
    By The University of Wisconsin. July. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The School for Workers, Publication (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: Labor Uses University, Publication (Box 74, Folder 37)
- Box: 74, folder: 38 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Recruitment to the Skilled Trades: A Study of a Segment of a Skilled Labor Market, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Norman F. Dufty. June 1967; an IRRI Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Recruitment to the Skilled Trades: A Study of a Segment of a Skilled Labor Market, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Norman F. Dufty. June 1967; copy; an IRRI Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Recruitment to the Skilled Trades: A Study of a Segment of a Skilled Labor Market, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Norman F. Dufty. June 1967; copy 3; an IRRI Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Recruitment to the Skilled Trades: A Study of a Segment of a Skilled Labor Market, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Norman F. Dufty. June 1967; copy 2; an IRRI Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Vocational Retraining of the Unemployed: An Evaluation, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Gerald G. Somers. April 1966; an IRRI Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: (delete), Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By (delete). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Report on the International Symposium on Public Employment Labor Relations, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Kay B. Hutchison. an IRRI Report; copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report on the International Symposium on Public Employment Labor Relations, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Kay B. Hutchison. an IRRI Report; copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Report on the International Symposium on Public Employment Labor Relations, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
    By Kay B. Hutchison. an IRRI Report; copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A Balanced Program in Employment Security, Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - Item 11: The "Bug-a-boo" of "the Welfare State", Publication (Box 74, Folder 38)
- Box: 74, folder: 39 (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Class Gets Members-Eye View of Unions, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Autumn, 1954; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 13, no. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Class Gets Members-Eye View of Unions, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Autumn, 1954; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 13, no. 1; copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: City Celebrates 4-Year Education Program, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. February 1954; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 12, no. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: City celebrates 4-Year Education Program, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. February 1954; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 12, no. 2; copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: UAW-CIO, School Hold Steward Conference, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Nov. 1953; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 12, no. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: UAW-CIO, School Hold Steward Conference, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Nov. 1953; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 12, no. 1; copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Annual Summer Institutes Underway Again, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. June 1953; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 11, no. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Regents Appoint New Workers School Director, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. November 1952; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 11, no. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: These Women "Organize" Their Conversation, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. March 1953; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 11, no. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Waukesha Unionists Go Back To School, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. May 1954; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 12, no. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Plan Full Program of Extension Classes, Publication (Box 74, Folder 39)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Autumn 1955; School for Workers Newsletter vol. 14, no. 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 74, folder: 40 (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: New Approaches to Increasing Productivity- Publication List, Publication (Box 74, Folder 40)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Center for the Study of Productivity Motivation Graduate School of Business. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mid-Year Report, Publication (Box 74, Folder 40)
    By The University of Wisconsin. Center for the Study of Productivity Motivation, The Graduate School of Business. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 1 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Freedom to Work, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    By S. A. Woods Machine Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 2 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Network News and Notes- Women in Corporate Management, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Patricia Swatfager. June 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Network News and Notes- Oral History Program on Women Farmworkers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Margo McBane. July 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Network News and Notes- Women in Corporate Management, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Patricia Swatfager. June 1978; copy. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 3 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Woodward Governors At Work, Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    By Woodward Governor Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 4 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Letter and Agreement From President to The Union of Woodward & Lothrop Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    By Woodward & Lothrop Corporation. Aug. 24, 1959. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 5 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 50 Years of Service 1917-1967, Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    By Workmen's Compensation Board of British Columbia. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, folder: 6 (Box 75, Folder 6)